https://www.zsoltgyarmati.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What is GDPR?
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union and the European Economic Area. Applied across Europe from 25th May 2018, implemented in Hungary by the Act 112 of 2011 on Data Protection Bill and is designed to give you more control over your personal data and to simplify the regulatory environment across the EU for data management, including how data is exported outside the EU.
Principles for Data Processing
This is the Privacy Statement and Data Protection Policy for Zsolt Gyarmati’s homepage. I will process your data in a fair, lawful and transparent manner. I will ensure and make every effort to ensure that data is accurate, and if it is not, I shall respond quickly to change it. I will process your data in a secure way, protecting against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage.
Visitors to my Website
When someone visits www.zsoltgyarmati.com I use a third-party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. I do this to find out things such as the number and residence of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. I do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting my website.
Links to Other Web Sites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.
Feedback
If you have any requests or comments about this policy, please contact me.
Copyright © 2020 Zsolt Gyarmati. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
